d-a-l.com 2014-12-02

# Privacy Policy | Techie7

Techie7.com (Previously D-A-L.com) is owned and operated by D24 MEDIA LTD

D24 MEDIA is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information received from you. We strictly adhere to the requirements of the data protection legislation in the UK.

The purpose of this statement is to explain to you what personal information we collect and how we may use it.

1\. When you use the “Contact Us” form on our website or register an account we may ask you for your Full Name and Email address.

2\. We use your personal information to contact you and follow up your enquiry.

3\. We do not sell, rent or exchange your personal information with any third party for commercial reasons.

4\. We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access in accordance with the UK data protection legislation.

5\. We do not collect sensitive information about you except when you specifically knowingly provide it.

6\. In order to maintain the accuracy of our database, you can check, update or remove your personal details by contacting us using the information below.

7\. We will not transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) without first obtaining your consent.

9\. If you have any questions about privacy please contact us using these details:

By Post:

**D24 MEDIA LTD, Dalton House, 60 Windsor Avenue, London, SW19 2RR, UNITED KINGDOM**

By Email: sales@d24media.com
